Guide to the Rice University Campus Photographer Files, 1970-2004 UA 188
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Campus Photographer Files
1970-2004
1990-2004
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 188
24 Linear Feet (48 Boxes)
An assortment of prints, photographs, negatives, and negative slides concerning the Rice University campus, student life, sports, professors, the O'Conner House, the Baker Institute, commencements, and other University events. Most of these photographs were taken by Campus Photographers Thomas LaVergne, Philip Channing, and Jeff Fitlow.
Historical note
These photographs span 35 years of Rice University history, and document annual events such as Commencement and Orientation Week, as well as campus buildings and people. Many are in color.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of 48 boxes documenting the activities of Rice University, with a focus on the student life through photography. It contains an assortment of prints, photographs, negatives, and negative slides concerning the Rice University campus, student life, sports, professors, the O'Conner House, the Baker Institute, commencements, and other University events. Dates range from 1970 – 2004.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored onsite at the Woodson Research Center.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges
Document Types
photographs; slides (photographs); negatives (photographic)
Places
Rice University
- Series I: Baker Institute events color snapshots, 79349
  - Baker Institute Event, 79350 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79351 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79352 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79353 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79360 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79361 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79362 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79363 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79364 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79365 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79366 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79367 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79368 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79369 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79370 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79371 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79372 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79373 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Baker Institute Event, 79374 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Series II: Rice campus people and places, 1970-2004, and undated, 79354
  - Negative Slides of Assorted Rice Campus and Student Life Activities, ~1970s., 79356 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - O'Conner House, 1970., 79357 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Negative Slides of Rice Campus and Buildings, March 22, 1988, 79358 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Negative Slides,1988, 79359 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - O'Conner House Negatives. March 15, 1990, 79377 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Student Life Photographs; Rice College Serveries. ~1990s, 79378 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Rice Baseball Team Negatives. 1992, 79379 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Rice University Assorted Negatives. 1992- 1993, 79380 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - O'Conner House Negatives. March 1994, 79381 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - O'Conner House Prints. 1994, 79382 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Negative Slides of Student Life. 1994-1998, 79383 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Seiichi Matsuda Portraits. Fall of 1995, 79384 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - O'Conner House Negatives. November 12, 1995, 79385 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Negative Slides. 1996, 79386 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Football Game against Southern Methodist University Negatives. 1998, 79387 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Mario Ramos Portrait Negatives, Rice Baseball Pitcher. 1999, 79388 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Dennis Huston Portrait Negatives. 1999, 79389 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Negative Slides of Student Life and Campus. 1999, 79390 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Football and Athlete Negatives. 2000, 79391 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Assorted Rice Photographs: Football, Modern Dance, etc. 2000, 79392 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Negative Slides of Student Life, Willy's Birthday, Baseball, etc. 2000, 2001, 79393 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Commencement (George H.W. Bush Speech) Negative Slides. 2000, 79394 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Rice Negative Slides. 2002, 79395 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Wild Art Negatives. 2002, 79396 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Admissions Stock Negatives. 2002, 79397 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - MLK Vigil Negatives. 2003, 79398 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Impact Awards Negatives, February 7, 2003, 79399 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - First African American Grad. 2004, 79400 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Rice Art Car Negatives. 2004, 79401 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Jones Ceo Amex Negatives. 2004, 79402 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - End of Campaign Negatives. 2004, 79403 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - FOF Gala Negatives. 2004, 79404 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Baker Dinners Negatives. 2004, 79405 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Shepherd School Quartet. 2002, 79406 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Baseball Negative Slides. Undated, 79407 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - MOB Negative Slides. Undated, 79408 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Campus Scenery Negative Slides. Undated, 79409 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Student Life Negative Slides. Undated, 79410 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - The Godwins Portraits, Photographs. Undated, 79411 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Prints of the O'Conner House. Undated, 79412 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Rice Assorted Negative Slides. Undated, 79413 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - "MOB MTV" Negatives. Undated, 79414 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - "Rice News" Negatives. Undated, 79415 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - "Old Rice Misc." Negatives. Undated, 79416 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "Ann Lugg Engineering" Negatives. Undated, 79417 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - "Malcolm Gillis" Negatives. Undated, 79418 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Assorted Unlabelled Negatives. Undated, 79419 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Rice Campus Prints, Assorted. Undated, 79420 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Series III: Addenda, transferred in 2011, 115370
  - Subseries A: Architecture and places, 115371
    - Aerial images, 116272 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Aerial images, 116273 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Architectural details - arches, 116269 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Architectural details - bas relief and carved brick, 116265 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Architectural details - column capitals, 116263 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Architectural details - doors and windows, 115519 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Architectural details - famous people and faculty carvings, 116262 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Architectural details - owls and plaques, 116268 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Architectural details - spires, 116266 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Architectural details - stairs, 116267 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Architectural details - general, 116270 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Architectural details - general, 116271 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Architectural details - general, 118637 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Architectural details - general, 118638 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - General campus views - black and white, 116275 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Outdoor scenes - animals, 118639 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Outdoor scenes - dusk, 118640 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Outdoor scenes - Fall, 118641 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Outdoor scenes - foggy, 118642 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Outdoor scenes - Sewall/Rayzor old road ROW, 118643 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Campus landscapes, 117634 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Entrance 1, 117636 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Academic quadrangle, 116277 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Architectural plans, 116274 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Abercrombie/Chemical Engineering, 116276 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Allen Center, 118644 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Anderson Hall, 116278 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Autry House, 116281 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Baker Institute, 116595 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Biochemistry, 118645 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Biology, 116282 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Bonner Nuclear Laboratory, 116285 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - George R. Brown Hall, 116286 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Herman Brown Hall, 116289 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Dell Butcher Hall, 116290 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Old Butcher Hall, 116292 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Campanile, 117985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Chemistry, 117979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Coffee House, 117544 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Cohen House, 116293 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - College dining halls, 117552 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - Baker, 116296 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Colleges - Brown, 116297 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Colleges - Hanszen, 116298 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Colleges - Jones, 118646 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Colleges - Lovett, 116299 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Colleges - Martel, 118064 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Colleges - Richardson, 116300 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Colleges - Wiess, 116301 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Duncan Hall, 116302 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Engineering Quad, 116306 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Fondren Library, 116307 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Fondren Library - proposed extension rendering, 117992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Geology, 116308 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Graduate House, 116309 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Gymnasium, 116598 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Herring Hall, 116310 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Huff House (formerly O'Connor House), 116752 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Humanities, 116313 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Human Resources Training Room, 116599 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Infotech Lab, 117587 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Jones School, 116316 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Keck Hall, October 2000; 116317 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Lovett Hall, 116318 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Lovett Hall, 118647 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Mechanical Engineering, 116319 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Mudd, 116320 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Physics lab (Herzstein Hall), 116594 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Rayzor Hall, 116324 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Rice Memorial Center, 116325 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Rice Memorial Center - chapel, 116327 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Rice Memorial Center - courtyard, 116326 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Rice Memorial Center - Willy's Pub, 116329 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - R Room, 1975, c. 1980; 116710 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Ryon Lab rendering, 117986 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Science Group - rendering, 117990 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Sewall Hall, 116331 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Sewall Hall - Art Gallery, 116332 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Shepherd School, 117656 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Space Science and Space Physics, 116597 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Stadium - 360 interior outtakes, 118275 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Stadium - external views, 116334 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Stadium - proposed cover rendering, 117991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Statues/sculptures on campus, 116336 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Symonds Laboratory, 116335 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Valhalla, 117545 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Willy's statue, 116337 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Willy's statue - turning of, 116339 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Woodson, 116596 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Campus - pre-construction, 118649 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Rice University forest/timber land, 116577 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Fred Hartman Bridge - with cranes, 118057 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Nichols-Rice-Cherry House, 116344 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Rice Village, 116345 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Vietnam Memorial, 116346 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - International University - Bremen Germany, 116343 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Houston and surrounding areas, 118648 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Houston and surrounding areas, 118650 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Subseries B: Events, 115520
    - Abercrombie Book Project, 116348 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Alumni events, 116464 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Alumni - Associates Honor Dinner, 116465 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Alumni - awards, Warwick, 2004; 116466 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Alumni College, 1997; 116467 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Alumni College, 1998; 116468 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Alumni College - A. Peterson, 2001; 116469 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Dinner, 2000; 116470 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Dinner - Owl Award, May 2001; 116471 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Alumni - Friends of Fondren Events, 116472 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Alumni - Homecoming, 1998; 116473 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Alumni - Homecoming, 1999; 116474 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Alumni - Homecoming, 2000; 116475 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Alumni - Leadership, 2002; 116476 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Alumni - Scholarship awards, 116477 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Archaeology, 116350 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Phil Archer/elected officials, December 8, 2000; 116579 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Associates Dinners, 116353 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Associates Night, 1998; 116354 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Associates Night, 2002; 116355 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Associates Night, 2003; 116356 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Awards, 116357 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Baker - events and people, 118979 (Box 16, Frame 1)
    - Baker - party portraits, 118652 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Baker - Poetry in Politics, February 1999; 118653 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Baker - Poetry in Politics 2, November 1999; 118654 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Baker - Americas Project, April 20-23, 1997; 118656 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Baker - Inaugural Annual Conference, November 13-14, 1995; 118657 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Baker - Inaugural Annual Conference, November 13-14, 1995; 118658 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Baker - Annual Conference, November 12-13, 1996; 118659 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Baker - Annual Conference, October 15-16, 1997; 118660 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Baker - Arab-American Lecture, 118661 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Baker - Conference, 1998; 118662 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Baker - Energy Conference - Toyota, December 7, 1998; 116360 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Baker - Energy Conference, 1999; 116361 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Baker - Environmental Conference, September 2000; 116362 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Baker - Korean Conference, 118663 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Baker - Police/African-American Community Conference, September 26, 1996; 118664 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Baker - Meeting with Leadership Rice, April 14, 1997; 118665 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Baker - Arab-Israeli Peace Process, February 5, 1998; 118666 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Baker - CIPE Energy Study Seminar, March 31-April 1, 1997; 118667 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Baker - Multicultural Banking Conference, September 16, 1996; 118668 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Baker - Health Policy Summit, October 30-31, 1997; 118669 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Baker - City Debate, 118670 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Baker - Reports, 118671 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Baker - Report #17, 118673 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Baker - Law Enforcement Summit, 118672 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Baker - Tenth Anniversary Gala and Conference, 118674 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Baker - Hong Kong, 116364 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Baker - Al-Attiyah, September 20, 1997; 118675 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Baker - Albright, Madeleine, 116754 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Baker - Annan, Kofi, April 1998; 116370 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Baker - Arafat, Yasir, 116753 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Baker - Ashwari, Hannan, October 18, 1996; 118676 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Baker - Baker, James A., 118677 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Baker - Boutros-Ghali, Boutros, 118682 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Baker - Bush, George, 118678 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Baker - Djerejian, Edward P., 118679 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Baker - Dustain, March 1999; 118680 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Baker - Eisenstat, April 1998; 118681 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Baker - Friedman, Thomas - "The Lexus and the Olive Tree", 118683 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Baker - Gillis, Malcolm, 118684 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Baker - Hamilton, 1999; 118685 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Baker - Kemp, Jack, 118686 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Baker - King, W.O., 118687 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Baker - Lane, Neal, April 1998; 118688 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Baker - Lebed, Gen. (Russia), March 1998; 118689 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Baker - Moussa, 2000; 118690 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Baker - Nazarbaev, November 20, 1997; 118691 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Baker - Pastronni, October 1999; 118692 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Baker - Powell, Colin, 118693 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Baker - Rabin, Leah, 118694 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Baker - Rabinovich, Hamar, June 12, 1996; 118695 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Baker - Reno, Janet, 1997; 118696 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Baker - Sabbagh, Hasib, September 17, 1997; 118697 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Baker - Schwartzkopf, 118698 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Baker - Shevardnadze, 118699 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Baker - Tarlov at ICF, December 13, 1999; 118700 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Baker - Troncale, John, 1999; 118701 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Baker - Wisner (Ambassador), September 24, 1997; 118702 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Baker - Wu, Wang, March 1998; 118703 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Baker - African Heads of State, 1999; 118704 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Baker - Coca-Cola CEO, March 1999; 118705 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Baker - Prince of Kuwait, November 1999; 118706 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Baker - Islamic Chair, 118707 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Baker - Visiting Ambassadors, 118708 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Baker - Ex-Secretary of Finance, 1998; 118709 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Baker - Former United States Librarian, March 1998; 118710 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Baker - Defense, November 20, 1998; 118711 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Baker - Society, 118712 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Beer Bike, 1974; 116711 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Beer Bike, 1975-1983; 118713 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Beer Bike, 1984; 118714 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Beer Bike, 1985; 118715 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Beer Bike, 1986; 118716 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Beer Bike, 1987; 118717 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Beer Bike, 1988; 118718 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Beer Bike, 1989; 118719 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Beer Bike, 1991; 118720 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Beer Bike, 1992; 118721 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Beer Bike, 1994; 118722 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Beer Bike, 1995; 118723 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Beer Bike, 1996; 118724 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Beer Bike, 1997; 118725 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Beer Bike, 1998; 118726 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Beer Bike, 1999; 118727 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Beer Bike, 2000-2004; 118728 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Beer Bike, undated; 118729 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Biochemistry, 116378 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Black Tie event, Spring 1989; 117977 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Brown Superior Teaching Award, 2004; 116757 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Kick-Off Black Tie, September 23, 2000; 116379 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Kick-Off Faculty/Staff, September 24, 2000; 116380 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Campus Torch Run, 2003; 116688 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Campus Tours, 116381 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Coloras Latinas, 117522 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Commencement, 1970s; 116382 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Commencement, 1982; 116383 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Commencement, 1983; 116384 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Commencement, 1984; 118068 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Commencement, 1985; 118730 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Commencement, 1986; 118732 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Commencement, 1987; 118733 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Commencement, 1988-1991; 118731 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Commencement, 1991-1992; 118734 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Commencement, 1992-1993; 118735 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Commencement, 1992-1993; 118736 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Commencement, 1993; 118737 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Commencement, 1994; 118738 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Commencement, 1995; 118739 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Commencement, 1996; 118740 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Commencement, 1997; 118741 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Commencement, 1998; 118742 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Commencement, 1999; 118743 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Commencement, 2000; 118744 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Commencement, 2001; 118745 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Commencement, 2002; 118746 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Commencement, 2003; 118747 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Commencement, 2004; 118748 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Commencement, undated; 118749 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Commencement for Bucky, 116580 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Concerts - Billy Joel, Elton John, the Eagles, 116385 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Concert - Monsters of Rock - Texas Jam of '88, 116386 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Country Music Festival - George Strait, Tim McGraw, 116387 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Cooper Conference, March 2004; 116388 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Crossfire, 116389 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Dances - Esperanza, Rondelet, 117561 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - DeLange Conference, 116391 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Development, 2000-2001; 116392 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Development - Amanda Brown - small events, 117584 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Development - Dedication of Practice Gym, 116390 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Development - Events and portraits, 116393 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Dore Dinner (Jackie), May 14, 2000; 116394 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Duncan Award, 116712 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Duncan Jubilee, 1997; 116728 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Duncan Oaks, 116395 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Earl Elliott Scholarship Fund - Jack Burke, 117523 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - East Side Mural, 2001; 118062 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Economic Summit, 118750 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Economic Summit, 118751 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Engineering, 1999; 116398 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Engineering Awards, 116397 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Engineering Majors Day, 117554 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Eyes of Texas, 2002; 116396 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Families Weekend, 116400 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Fireman Memorial, 2000; 116401 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Firing Line, 116402 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Freshman Recruiting Dinner, 1996; 116403 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Friends of Fondren, 116407 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Friends of Fondren - British Book (development), 1999; 116404 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Friends of Fondren Gala - Hoby, 1999; 116406 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Golden R, 116478 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Habitat for Humanity, 116408 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Habitat for Humanity - Carter's visit, 116409 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - High Endeavor, 116410 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Homecoming, 1994; 116411 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Homecoming, 1996; 118752 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Homecoming, 1997; 118753 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Homecoming, 1998; 118754 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Homecoming, undated; 118755 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - J. Howell Press Conference - Big Pencil, February 1999; 116412 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Humanities Luncheon 10/20, 116413 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Ice Cream Social, 2002; 116713 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Inaguration - Rupp, October 1985; 116414 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Insurrection, 1918; 117457 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Jam Fest, 2002; 118058 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Jones School, 1999; 116415 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Jones School, 2000; 116692 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Jones School, 2001-2002; 116416 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Jones School, 2003; 116417 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Jones School, undated; 116418 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Jones School - Cocktail Career Fair, 116420 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Jones School - Dedication, 116421 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Jones School - Dinner - O Room, December 2001; 116422 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Jones School - Enron Speaker, 116423 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Jones School - MBA Orientation, July 2001; 116426 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Jones School - Minority MBAs, 116427 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Jones School - Recruitment Dinner, 116428 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Jones School - Sommers Seminar, January 21, 2001; 116429 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Jones School - Tour with Dean, August 2001; 116430 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - KTRU Music Fest, 2004; 118061 (Box 28, Folder 1)